Voices collide, the storm and the flame, laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive, in Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's awake? We're awake, who's afraid? Let it break, from shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown.
The Psyche awakens, you're never...
The Unexpected.
psyches show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand but angels are
Dan
What's up?
Samantha.
I love your name.
I'll just say,
it's a familiar name.
Hi, thank you.
I had a bad,
I don't want to say too much,
but I picked up,
Jamie and I were talking,
and I picked up the phone,
and I was like,
she turned the camera on.
Oh, God, that's funny.
No, that's funny.
Sorry.
Oh, God, okay.
How are you?
Hi, guys.
You like the song?
I like it.
There's two versions.
As soon as 10 people get here.
Hey, hey J-Dog. What's up, dude?
So what do I have that picture? Oh another picture. Oh, oh shit. No, no, please don't please don't say it
Taste the biscuit
That's embarrassing. Oh my god. I
Don't like that. I don't like that at all. Okay. Hold on
I pushed the wrong button
Welcome to Psyche Awakens TV
More than a livestream, it's a gathering in the shadow in the light. We face chaos, comedy, and the unknown together.
With open panels that never shy away from the truth, I am Psyche, your guide through tarot, prophecy, and the unfiltered clash of voices.
Tonight, we're stepping into the panel verse where allies and trolls alike reveal themselves in every card turn.
Every word spoken is part of the story.
So stay sharp, stay curious, because once the gates open, anything can happen.
The show is about to begin. Let's go.
Thank you, Jesus.
Jesus Christ. I'm actually saying his name. Hold on a second.
Uh, one more thing. Oh, hey, hey, babe.
Lola, Lola, hey Lola. Lola, how are you?
Come here, baby. What is this picture?
Oh, I got it. Okay. Let me delete that.
Hold on a second.
Part two.
every scar a secret carved in stone carrying stones that cut to the
Ta-da
Hi everybody, what's up? Hey, yes
Charisma money for 20. What's up guys? Hi?
Hi guys, what's up?
What you want to see Lola? I'm gonna see Miss Lola
Like do I genuinely enjoy what?
Oh
This is tricks his mom
Hey, can you really enjoy what?
This is what Gish looks like with the avatar.
I'm sorry, not really, just the emoji.
Hey, baby.
Lola, I can't see the chat when you're doing that.
Hi.
Need a little more, Sammy, Sony?
Hey, Electra, what's up?
Taste the biscuit.
Hold on, everybody.
Let's say it, let's say it all together.
Taste the biscuit.
I can do it all at once. I have to stop. I have to stop myself. Stop it. Stop it. It's not funny. It's not funny.
I don't get it. Stop. I don't get it. I don't get it.
Don't understand what it means. Stop saying it.
Not sure why did yeah, just like Eric. I wish I had some mushrooms fuck
Unfortunately I had to settle for
Coffee and weed. Oh
It's a biscuit gang. Hey Jesus
Hey Jesus, what do you have to say for yourself Jesus?
Welcome to psyche awakens TV
More than a livestream, it's a gathering in the shadow and the light. We face chaos, comedy, and the unknown together.
With open panels that never shy away from the truth, I am Psyche, your guide through tarot, prophecy, and the unfiltered clash of voices.
Tonight, we're stepping into the panel verse where allies and trolls alike reveal themselves in every card turn.
Every word spoken is part of the story.
So stay sharp, stay curious, because once the gates open, anything can happen.
The show is about to begin. Let's go.
So I don't know if you I don't I want to show it if the lecture didn't see this I'm gonna play it again
I'm not not I'm not the song but it's the
Hey, lol, hey, lol, lol, what if they called you a low cow would you like that? No fuck you?
Oh my gosh, you know don't call people low cows. That's so rude. Her name is Lola not low cow, okay?
Get it right
Taste the biscuit
Let me see
Okay, yeah, I'm gonna play the um
This thing again
This is so funny. I mean, I love this guy that he made these great videos
It's a pretty short video. It's only 12 minutes. Okay. Oh, hold on a second. It's got everything. It's got everything
You like a little
You would like a big
O fish woman. Oh my god, there's it just close your eyes. Hold on
Yeah, so let's watch this again if you didn't see it the first time.
Share the screen, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Thank you. Hey Saki, why don't you come up and show us your fucking beta pose with your little American flag song bitch?
Seas is cooking today.
The fuck you weirdo?
Why don't you go lay in a fucking puddle a fucking god damn kitty litter fucktard?
Yeah, I mean realize you fucking bitch the only reason why she's over there
It's because you have an audience sometimes and she wants to fuck beta over you didn't realize her contents beta it ain't you face boy
It's not you and your little fucking weird ass pussy cat you got over there.
I have a question for you, Psyche.
Are you that broke that you actually have to charge people to open a fucking panel?
I mean are you really that goddamn broke that you have to charge people to start fucking
No, he's just that he's just apathetically disparate. Did you guys see his new advertisements?
Come join my popular panel
I'll give you readings, but I don't even know what the fucking death card means
But I can show you my fucking tank dressed in american flag in my baby
And that that is it. That is the real site. That is the real site people
And then we do, so you do what I say, you do what I say.
No, I watch the fucking clip.
I watch fucking beep.
I watch fucking Janney.
I watch fucking trip kick because I'm
watching four hours of some gay guy pretending
to be a psychic fucking beg for money for fucking fish tacos.
Get the fuck out of here.
I forgot what pad I'm on.
It's a fucking weird curve.
It's all up in there all the time.
Fucking weird
Let me tell you something if Jimbo was up there telling women that the only way they could get up on the fucking panels
If they show their tits, they would fucking roast him
About being a sexual
Fucking psyche can sit up there and say well you can
If you show your fucking shlong you you're gross out motherfucker
He's laying on a fucking puddle of kitty litter fucking talking about how he's a devil you're fucking weirdo, bitch
The only reason why you get any attention that you do is because you're a
So so shannon shannon can he come up here and give you a a tarot reading i'll pay for it
Oh, please allow him. So i would love to fucking rip his little american flag shit up his ass
You hear that site? I see you five dollars for a tarot for shannon. You gotta come up here and do it
Yeah, let's see how will you read tarot. Tell me what the death card's about again
Because you totally fucked that up
I don't know
You so you say he's been reading them wrong the whole time. Yes, he doesn't know what the fuck
Terrell in his name he
how's he trying to act like he's a celebrity and people want to see him when he's looking
with a bunch of old women fucking cats sleeping on fucking kitty litter and writing a fucking e-buck
to get fish tacos are you guys really buying that shit? you're killing them
give her a read if she say you don't read the cards right oh my god prove to us that you read the
Hey, that's because I don't got some readings from you, man.
Hey, did you give him me roll readings?
I'm going to tell you what they really fucking mean,
because he goes all over the place like he's full of shit.
He doesn't know what the fuck any of them fucking mean.
You know how long I've been watching Tarot.
Tell me again how the death card is.
What was it?
You said it was.
It was about something, someone in your life leaving you.
Are you talking about Santa Santa you can't tell me because I'm telling you I got I pay for readings from him
So you telling me that he read to me the wrong shit
The one fucking time I saw him reading he said the death card was about leaving something behind or whatever
I thought about the death cards about it's about new beginnings
It means the end of a fucking right cycle in your life in a beginning one, so I can tell you right now
He pulls out his little Disney princess cards talking some shit about the four cups
I'm gonna fuck her doesn't know shit about cards at least get out the key
They give you in a fucktard and read what they mean
$5 for the cats yet. I've never seen him buy shit for his cats ever I've seen him buy an e-bike
I've seen him fucking ride to the fucking beach and buy fish tacos. I've seen him try to get the butcher's fucking phone number
I've seen him fucking pull his legs up like he was a fucking female in his little fucking red, white, and blue panties.
But I'm seen doing shit by shit by lick fucking goddamn snatches of women that he think are more popular than him.
Hey, where's your trilogy out there? Where's, where's Psyche's beauties? Not one of those fuckers talk to you anymore, dumb shit.
And that's for a fucking goddamn friendship.
Here's the truth psyche. I'm gonna give you a fucking truth. You know what? You were you were cannon fodder
Be to brought you to be to brought those fucking people to your fucking place because she didn't want you to fucking have a real stream
She didn't bring you to saying man's
She didn't fucking bring them to fucking capes. She didn't bring them
She brought them to your channel and none of us knew the
fuck you were you were just one of her weirdos that she fucking had in her
back pocket so instead of losing her channel she could fuck with yours good
Cunt card for her. So she got that. That's her first car. Okay. Yeah, exactly. That's her only card.
I do know how to reach it so you can read it right yeah yeah let's see the card yeah
let's see it work I can't but it's not appropriate for Kate show I had to have more respect for
Kate than to get her up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up
here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up
here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here
Okay.
up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up here up
Wow.
You got me there.
You got me there, bitch.
I think that was shit.
Oh, my God.
My cast sounds better than you, bitch.
Why don't you stay out of Bootsy and it won't smell like shit.
I don't even know you.
Like, what are you talking about?
If you don't even know me, how can you talk?
You're talking about some character you see on.
This is, this is, this is Shannon.
She's a queen of the, of Gen X.
She ain't queen of fish.
She's queen of the sea.
I'm certainly not the queen you are bitch boy that's for sure
Never be the queen I am bitch
Yeah, don't worry. I don't want to be you. I didn't realize that turning your couch into a fucking litter box made you
In my video, okay
Why don't you eat back a little bit?
I don't know how she knows me.
How does she know so much about me?
She sounds, she's like, I don't, I know zero about her.
Well, because you get the lift because you're an LOL cow.
You're LOL cow, so they clap.
Really, well milk me bitch, milk me.
How about some fresh grass?
How about some green grass?
It really hurt.
Honestly, because you're having a little hitch fit.
I don't know if I can see up there, kid.
Okay.
Go, go be sad.
Go be sad.
I know you're the only member here.
You have to respect me a little bit.
Sigh, kid.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
What did you pull it I had a premonition I was gonna hear some dumb
thoughts screaming about me on a show and then I came over here and
hear what I think I'm
perfect.
You asked for premonitions.
I'm perfectly.
You have all thoughts.
Yeah.
Oh gosh.
Either way make sure you pull out the key for the card so you actually
know what they mean.
I don't need to wait for the garbage.
I've been doing tears and I was eight years old.
Okay.
So by the way.
And every year old is so gifted doing peril.
door started. It's called like, you know, I've been doing tarot since I was two. So I win.
You haven't been doing tarot at all. Have you? Yes, I have. I do tarot every fucking day.
Okay, well, you know you should be careful about disparaging fellow readers the karma's really bad on that. Oh, yeah, okay
I'll worry about my karma as you're spreading
Okay, give a show like how do you know you have the public fucking stream that everybody clips because you're a total retard
I have a reading part of you. If you want to fucking shut up. I'll give you a good reading
But if you don't want to shut up
Little mad
Deuterine, Psyche, Deuterine.
Mary made me, so, okay, so I will,
I'll do the rejuvenation.
Okay, this for Shannon, this Shannon's rejuvenation.
And so you received justice for something
in the recent past.
I don't know if that was a successful court case
or something in the recent past,
but you, something was made fair for you.
And you've also got like,
oh, you see all these options available to you now
because of this, but it's a lot of confusion
because of it, because there's so many,
you're gonna wanna pick the one
that you most gravitate towards.
That looks like something to do with love
because there's like a two of cups,
two equals, um, meeting and, you know, starting something that can grow into something bigger.
You're also coming up as queen of wands. And so you've got a lot of good fiery power.
This is also like the Norman Bates mom card, okay, whatever.
Also, because you are
I like some more about that card.
What's the more about the card? Well, it says courage, confidence, independence, right?
It says Norman Bates is mom. That's what it says.
The givers got psycho, that's Norman Bates' mother, okay?
That's queen of fucking wands.
Somebody go look up with a queen of wands representation,
isn't it?
It says, courage, confidence, independence, okay?
Yeah, that's what it says, okay?
Yes, so that's that's not a date mom. Okay, lie some more because it's not going for you. Go ahead. Okay. Well, whatever whatever
I'm gonna do this quick reading for you. Okay. Finally, we have the ten of the ten of wands
Which means you've been carrying some burdens you've been carrying other people's burdens
Maybe because you're in the screen energy like a lot of people go to you for help and things like that
No, you don't know but it is very heavy. It's like how do you got the burdens going on in the future?
It is correct. The queen of wands is passion, confidence, charisma and
Fierce independence symbolizing someone who boldly pursue
their dreams with courage and enthusiasm this card encourages you to
Authentic self embrace creative endeavors
Okay
Yeah, you're doing it since you were eight, but you can't even get the cards right.
I got all the cards.
You don't even know to look to see if the cards reversed, you fucking tarred.
I told them reverse, so they're not reversed, you fucking tarred, okay, anyway, they'd come
out reversed, they wouldn't just turn them upside down on my own, okay, well, anyway,
you know nothing about tarot, so whatever, so, okay, thank you, K, for having me on.
I guess that just leaves one score at the center.
You can't hurt me.
Then let this be our final battle.
are some people like just stupid I mean I say oh make your own kind
To understand I was the content you don't see that yeah, and when don't call my cats weirdos with the fucking
That's the worst thing she said. I was the content that was me. Do you see you see me up there?
I was the star of that clip. I don't think that loudmouth bitch was I think I was
Yep, I agree
Fuck
Yeah, it was tripkicks video, right so
Yeah, it was a double re-stream actually gonna play my song again
Taste the biscuit
Yo, what's up?
Okay, hmm. I'm in a good mood. So I'll do
Thank you, Jamie. Thank you. I
Did like it. I love it. I love it. I'll do five dollar readings. I'll do free readings, but
If you'd like a longer reading I'll do $5 and plus I can put my camera like I can do the reading on the table here
So I can show you the cards close up and everything
Yeah, I do have this like new like rules set of rules kind of let me see the harassment of oh my gosh the harassment
Oh poor woman can't stand up for herself. She needs to help her. Oh, no
You're just embarrassing her go the fuck away die your sacrifice to the cult
Mini-Haden
Dick cheese
Bye-bye
Go lick her butt, okay? Get away from me. I don't need
Some midget named Hayden in here bothering me
Motherfucker
Go lick me as biscuits, okay? I
Know you want to okay?
You know what what do you want to do everybody one?
Two, what does he want to do one two three?
Taste the biscuit
Exactly
Yes, okay
Uh oh, Team Vita, get the fuck out of here.
Oh my gosh, look at this loser.
Look at this loser.
Yep, I think we need the Psyche Hate Club song
because it's just been so much hate today, hasn't there?
I mean, this guy asked for it, guys.
He asked for it.
He begged for it.
Come on, I have to play.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I have to play it.
Hold on.
I have to.
He just wants it.
Okay, I'm gonna play it.
There you go. Oh, oh wrong one. Hold on. That was the wrong one. I think it's this one.
Christine's mad about crystal Tony's just full of it
Braun's chicken struts around but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet pea is gone south
Welcome to the
Welcome to the...
Thank you. Thank you. Appreciate it. There we go. It's the rim reaper in the chat and the rim
reaper on a panel. Um, yeah. Anyone want a rim job? Free.
People that say I don't have anything free, free rim jobs.
Hold on. Where am I? I need to turn up on my camera. Oh, there I am. It's in my gorgeous face.
Do I look good in red?
How do I look?
I mean, I look okay.
I think I look okay.
Oh, okay.
Oh, oh my goodness.
Oh, gosh.
How was your day, guys?
It was a little bit, you know.
It was actually a good day.
It was actually, what's that song?
Today was a good day.
I don't know, Ice Cube things or something.
Hey, Chanel.
I like the way Chanel.
She gets rewarded
Team Psyche
Team Psyche there's benefits to Team Psyche, you know
Like
You're actually a cool person beat is my content
Do you see her anywhere around you? I mean what there was one line in the song
Be better be this bitter Betty again. How is that Mike? Oh, thank you. God, you go God. He's got he's good
God he's good. I love God
Unfortunately with Alexander McQueen
We had a little issue right you had a little issue this morning
He decided to start streaming which is really good. And then he's like he was so excited
He's like, hey, I like you. I'm streaming over and stuff. I went over there. His stream was called psyche awakens TV
Oh, excuse me
You rolled a good J today was a good J. It's a good day. Good J, right?
Yeah, and so then Alex
Started hiding this like a really cute girl named Guadalupe guacamole
She was
Like he's like oh this bit. I was like Alex
You're not supposed to as a mod be calling for a bit just clicked for me as like over the mod shouldn't be calling chat bitches and then
She came up on panel because he did hide her
You know what?
Go out of loopy guacamole. It was like the cutest little avocado pit I've ever met in my life and she was so sweet so nice
Just like the sweetest part like
He was like, oh, he's just like saying horrible thing and she was so nice and
She wanted a reading and I did a reading and she loved it and I was like
How many people the hot he had 60 people hidden?
Yeah, see burning joint yeah burning joint gets it like him and you know somebody I'll pool name remaining
He was oh, I don't I'm gonna do the boys don't do the boys, but it's like why
Don't I just talk instead of just like making a like writing a song and putting it to like music and stuff?
Why don't I just talk I?
Don't know if you've ever heard of like music. It's like there's like a you know, it's like it
You know catharsis or something. I don't know
I think music is like a little bit different than just talking right and I get to express myself of course
If I was to like write this song and then like you know higher
a string orchestra, rent out a studio, you know,
$50,000 later in like up two months
when everyone's forgotten the whole situation.
Oh yeah, then I can release the song and write.
No, I'd rather like be able to like, you know,
put it out immediately.
I don't know.
I think they sound pretty fucking good.
I think I have a good taste in music.
I don't know.
I think I'm like musical.
I'm not, I don't play really instruments,
but I can sing and I can write music.
I mean, I can write songs.
I'm not really good at playing instruments.
So, but I'm still able to make songs now, right?
I don't know.
It's like, someday it will click for people.
You can put human intellect plus AI equals
Quality content maybe maybe maybe just maybe maybe maybe maybe I don't know. I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong, right?
It's not like
You know artists don't you know Britney Spears voice, you know, is that her natural voice?
You know, it's like all synthesized and fucking
It's full of AI. I mean people dumb. I mean really are people fucking dumb. Yes, there's you know
Great classic rock stuff from like the 70s and stuff, but it pretty much everything passed then even the 70s was pretty yeah
Anything that's recorded pretty much has a lot of work, you know
electronic work done to it so
There's something so wrong with that. I just don't get it. Like what's the problem?
Obviously, maybe I'm hating a nerve with some people because it's getting a little like, you know
Close to home. It was just like crap then it's like why would they even bother like caring, right?
It was just like garbage and it's all my ear. Nope
Hardly no one left to chat it was like so
No, maybe there's something to this whole like, you know technology. I mean you are after all on a computer
We're on computers and stuff, right? I don't know
So remember these to use like paper
I suppose I'm gonna go get like the little like chisel and a stone and I'm gonna start writing like oh
That's the only true way to write right I need to be using a chisel and a stone
You know, maybe I shouldn't even use the alphabet. I could just like, you know, I don't know. Oh
Gosh people understand. I mean you guys understand but
People that are dissing me don't understand. Okay, so I'm gonna do a collective reading for the chat and
Then I'll do individual readings for free. But if you'd like a longer reading
I do have the cash up someone put that and I'll do it for five dollars
I'll do it like at least 12 cards for you. I mean
I'll do like three to five for free. Okay
Don't say like I'm just like and plus I've done so many more free readings than
Hey, I mean, it's like I do a lot of free readings. So it's like what what is it?
I mean, it's like it does take energy. I do a good job
People just have so many every like little thing people want to complain about right?
So how about like we just have fun and plus I'm going to be definitely
Putting more emphasis on the tarot from now. I like some of the drama, but it's like it's getting a little bit stale the drama. I
Mean if I have to like argue with you know
imbeciles for another day about
fish tacos and speedos and which I
obviously I
Fucking oh
Beated isn't do taro. Come on. She does her she does huff is stuff. I mean, she's just she's ridiculous
Anyway, I mean she's fine. Okay, what do I got?
She was like, oh, I get here better than you
Whatever go do Carol
Where are they your own show?
We're about my titles of my shit and stuff. How about just everyone worry about their own shit?
So done with it. Okay, then do for the chat
Okay.
Oh, wow, okay.
Where do we got?
What do we got?
Oh, let's see.
We're starting out with judgment.
Okay, so judgment's being called.
And I really felt that today,
like today was the day of revelation
and there's the angel blowing the trumpet, right?
You know the angel blows the trumpet of revelation. I'm sorry. It's not I need to fix
There we go
The angel blows the trumpet of revelation. Okay. Oh fuck. Oh god dang it
Camera is frickin I need a new camera
There
Okay, so we got judgment. Okay, we got the judgment card Angel has blown the trumpet
Yeah, that's cutting it. Okay, so there okay and
Then we have a victory the six of wands. Okay, but victory at what cost, okay, and so we always have to be
We always have to be
Cognizant of what hit the victory cause and is it worth even the battle because some battles aren't worth it
And look at this victory what the victory of the robots and they are just like obeying and stuff like that and walking
You know like sheep and stuff like that. And so we want to be careful
about
Mmm, what we will sacrifice for our victory, but I feel like there's been a lot of victories in here in a good way and
Probably financial because it looks like we're able to oh shit. I apologize. See what here's what the problem is
Trixie I love my lovely Trixie. I love my cat
Well, okay, you have to settle for the grim re of the grim revert I'm talking about this
The reading okay, so anyway, we have the Six of Panicles which is a spirit of charity
That means that we're able to be generous, actually, and know who to give to and we are able to give because there's some kind of material success.
Then we have the King of Swords and the Night of Swords together.
Okay, the King of Swords is a very, very smart guy.
He's probably a Gemini.
Probably like Gotti, you know?
He might do the Gotti.
is head on. I'm going to continue to try to get my camera working, but, you know,
little trixty is biting on my camera.
Oh, okay, so let me just fix...
Embarrassing. Oh, so embarrassing.
Oh, I just see people outside. And I can't even change the...
This is just nice.
Okay, but the king with the knight of swords, it's like the king of swords is able to call upon this knight of swords to do his dirty work
This knight of swords as an executioner kind of guy. And so we're like able to actually like, you know
Make some boss moves here, and it's like we're actually using our intelligence and this knight of swords
You know he's gonna chop off some heads, you know, we got some ambition
You know knight of swords is like a little of the king in training. He's got the ambition
He's
In a drive to succeed and everything the king is more sitting on his throne, you know just making the orders
Okay, now what we have next we have the three of wands. Okay, so the three of wands is about
leaving, leaving our home base and going out and going to this adventure. Okay, so
it's a call to adventure. But what is this adventure? We have the moon. Okay, so
it's maybe something to do with the nighttime or something, the more occult
area, or it's just something that's not to be revealed yet, just like the moon
goes through cycles.
The you know everything will be revealed in time, but it will take a little bit sometimes
But just rest assured things will be revealed and look at this
We went to see under the moon and then look we got the six of swords the six of swords is leaving
Rough waters going to calm our waters. So whatever our journey is it's gonna lead to a
To a like a more friendly place. We're just taking a bath in the water. Okay, then we got the star card
Okay, the star card she came to earth driven by an insatiable desire to continue the cycles of fertility
Okay, so that we got fertility we got make a wish star power
And you know what at the end of this we have the world and the world is completion of a successful cycle
I think this is all almost in one day all this happened right a lot happened today
But I feel like I've come through some kind of cycle.
I don't know if you guys felt it today.
And we are also ending the month.
I think, what time is it?
Oh, it's 12.04.
That's good news.
That's good news because I can do something right now.
But the world is the successful completion of a cycle.
It says the end is here, but.
You know every end is a new beginning and that bitch that was talking about the death card doesn't mean leaving something behind
But then she's like it means starting something new well when you start something new it does mean leaving something behind you dumb
Chua, okay, and so I don't know she says she uh
She has done tarot every day or whatever. I do tarot every day as well. I do it on TikTok. I do it here
I've done it since I was eight years old. She's done it since she was two. So I guess she wins
Well, she wins the weight contest definitely she weighs about 300 pounds more than me and she wins the
ugly bitch contest because she looks like Dom DeLauisse and Bruce Valance had a child.
Okay, and so I do apologize my camera went out. Let me try to unplug it and plug it back in. We'll
see if that works. If not then
Apologize I just well you heard it the first time there, but you saw the cards you get you get the idea
I will make sure that doesn't fuck up this time
It's technical difficulties guys, right? Let's see Shannon and be oh my gosh
Who owns me? I'm Joe you know who I own Joe. Oh, yeah, I own you Joe
Go suck my nuts
31st, 30 days has September.
So there's not 31 days in this month.
So we are actually October 1st, if I'm correct.
Yes, we are October 1st, not the 31st, hold on.
Oh, now to the 31st, you're right, okay.
All the souls I have surround you, protect you, say,
oh, thank you, Grim, thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I can't wait for Halloween, I love Halloween.
Thank you, Smith.
free reading or you can hit the cash up if you'd like a longer reading and I
will make sure it doesn't go out again I know now I just like I think it was
because I was moving the camera around and then it like goes out cuz you know
Trixie kind of chewed on my cord a little bit let's see oh Jamie would like
one okay Jamie when they Jamie oh you love Halloween okay
Grimm, would you like a reading?
Yann, Smith, can you hear me okay?
Let me just put this there.
Yeah, I mean, I do free readings.
I mean, people say, oh my God.
It's like,
if I, I mean, people are just like so cruel to me, right?
You'd like a reading?
Okay.
You see how I mean I was trying to do and guys I did I tried to do a nice reading for that woman
And I don't want to like you know keep bad-mouthing her, but she was fucking annoying
Audios and videos good. Okay. Thank you bluebeam
What is my Halloween costume this year?
Do I have my mask around might be this mask? I don't know. I have this great mask. I have my free stuff
This is my like king of hell
I would love to do drag again and like be Lilith, but this is actually made in
Italy. It's quite a nice mask, okay? Aren't I handsome?
Oh, thank you, Grim. Thank you. I appreciate that. And that's why Alex won't be a mod anymore. It's because, you know, that woman really enjoyed. She's on panel right now. Go make a good, I don't think so. She asked me to stay away. So I'll stay away. I'm not going to like go push myself on people. She's welcome here anytime.
Unfriendly and I know everyone here would be respectful to her
But it's like she would have me on her panel with like five people
They'd all have their microphones at the maximum volume because this happened like the last like ten times, right?
I'd have just people yelling at me calling me disgusting calling me drifter
Call it just like, you know something they can she can she wants to say that to me face a bit like just her me
That's but she's not gonna have her little minions
Calling me names and like, you know all piling on me. So she's welcome if she'd ever want to
But she, I don't think she, she obviously, she says, she says she's a woman to contact her. So
I'm gonna respect that. I respect, um, I respect your wishes. Your wish is my command.
What did Alex do? Alex just, he, he was, he's, he hid like 60 people.
I pushed myself on the vampire lady, I am pushed shit.
I was her mod, okay?
I donated a lot of money to her
and got a lot of readings from her
and she's a less experienced reader than I am.
But I did kind of like have a little bit of a crush
even though I'm gay.
I do like, you know, I'm attracted to succubuses.
I have a succubus tattooed on myself.
She just reminds me a little bit of my inner self who's like Lilith, you know
She's absolutely not Lilith, but yeah, yeah
Alex hid like 60 people and he hid like people that want readings and the friends of mine and stuff like that
I just you know and
You know he actually he started going his own live and it's like that's fine
But he like got stream yard. He isn't he I went to his lives. I watched it
He's not talking at all. He's not has not on video
It's just a blink of blank screen the whole time the entire show. It's just I went through the whole thing
There's no not talk once and I was like Alex
Why aren't you talking because you know how do you obviously use a microphone and like stuff?
He's like, oh, I just want to hide people. I just want people to go there. So I can hide them. I
mean
That's a little bit
Cuckoo Alex. I love you. I love you. You're trying to catch when he goes live you subscribe
You don't know why yeah
I mean money just be where all he wants to do is hide you all he's gonna do is just hide you
He's not gonna say hi or anything. You're just gonna hide you in the blank screen. It's like I was like I was like
This is it's just a little bit nutty to me. I don't know. I don't just didn't make sense. I was like Alex
What is the point of just hiding?
Without not you're I mean, it's gonna talk to them and like and then I was like and just don't name the stream psyche awakens TV
Like name it open panel or something. He's like, I don't want people to come but if they come I'm gonna hide them I
Was like why did I mod him I must have
Been really drunk or something when I don't know
But I do I do like him
I took away his wrench and then someone timed him out for like 24 hours because he's not in the he's not in the band people
So he must be just timed up because he's just disappeared and so I hope he comes back
I'm gonna pin the link and anybody's welcome up for a reading of course free readings for all
Unless you'd like a longer one or maybe like to tip if you like if you really like your reading
I do appreciate anything, but let me see. I'm gonna invite guests of course
You know you're also welcome just to come chat and stuff
But if you're like if you really don't fuck with like the occult or like
Esoteric or New Age or even like just religion or in history
I mean that's like in something in something besides just me and beauty yelling at each other
I'm done with that. It's just like that is just so boring to me. I'm sick of it. I don't know if that's I mean that's
And it's like, I prefer to do my trade.
And so I'm going to be, do I have my,
I do have like, and I know there might be
one misspelling on this thing,
but this is like, I have some kind of rules.
These are, I'm going to have to modify these a little bit.
Like we can go through these.
Psyche awakens panel code of conduct.
Okay.
And by the way, you know, it's a little bit like, you know,
I'm going to have a little bit relaxed rules.
It's not like, you know,
Because I have to like be able to call people names occasionally not like you know
Just because of it so many trolls so I have to be able to like fight back and so it's people debate
Let's see. Let's see. So but respect the space no slander harassment or personal attacks. Okay
Let's not get too personal, right? Okay, but that's the you know, just follow these rules stay on the topic
You know, we discuss tarot
We discussed the occult and community
Keep it relevant see community. So that means that we can discuss the drama shit and stuff
But just like not all that's not all about that and it is within a cult twist
And I'm gonna be pulling cards on like different streamers and like different
Things like that. Oh, by the way, I did invite Q here. I talked to Q today. He was really nice to me. Actually
I went to his chat. He got his channel
He got like two strikes or something because
Something I don't know why it was just really strange reason, but I
Went and found his backup channel. It's called at fish taco 10 or something
I don't know where he got that name
But I thought they were getting a giveaway free fish tacos and I went there and Q was there and I was like oh my gosh
But he was like is that the real psyche? I was like yes
And I was like and then he was like but then I was kind of the only person there because this is a backup channel
And so he's like oh he got bored with me. So he ended I was like come to my chat
Maybe he'll be back, okay? One mic at a time, right? Don't shout over others. Oh, this is a great rule
I love this and
supporters and
And guess and bite a guess only right supporters
I don't want just fucking people here, you know trolling me on the my own panel, right?
Then we have the true strikes rule readings are for members or donators, okay, or
Free readings for everyone too, but they're gonna be shorter readings. Okay, and then violation equals you're muted second time
You're booted mooted booted and third time
Tooted and no debate and then this is a space for truth creativity and respect trolls get no stage
I mean, okay. Well, we're gonna be kind of loose with this because it's like I think everyone here is kind of
Has a little bit of troll blood in them. I have I have some royal troll blood
And so, you know, I understand having a little bit, but it's like it's not just about like calling people fucking
you know
bitches and
American flag Speedos like I get called
Where is everybody? Let me just say I'm inviting the guests again. I mean, it's fine
I mean, what do you think I expected wearing American flag speeders and putting my legs behind my head?
Of course, I knew that it's like, hey Marcy, of course
I knew that it would be ridiculous and you know, I look I look stupid
But isn't it kind of like life about like, you know embarrassing yourself sometimes, but I wasn't really that embarrassed
Obviously, okay, I did it. It was kind of like
I'll do the most stupid embarrassing thing I can think of,
and then it's like, what?
Now what?
It's like, what else can I do?
The only thing I can do is get naked.
I'm not gonna get naked, you know?
So, I pretty much embarrassed myself as much as I can.
Hi, Marcy, how are you?
Good seeing you.
Great seeing you, and yeah, I've had an interesting day.
Who would like to come up and say hi? I haven't seen a lot of you for a while. I love to talk to oh
Grimm I'm gonna mod Grimm because he's a good friend of mine
I did have I did like you know I talked to somebody they're like well on my show
I have like they told me that they have like five mods and then I like counted my mods
I'd like over like 60 mods and I didn't know who half of them were and so I
Just was like you know
I'm modding a bunch of people.
So I'm sorry if I did I'm on somebody
that should have had a mod.
Let me see.
Put you on the IP2, by the way, the trolls.
Yeah, I am starting my own network called the Psycheverse.
Yeah, Grim is good people's.
And I wanna help all of you guys.
And so if you guys have a channel,
when I get the site up and running,
and I'm gonna work on it a little bit,
but when I get the site up and running,
I'm gonna be happy to put your I'm gonna actually show you what it looks like guys if you haven't seen it
This is just the prototype and it's like I'm still working on it. It's not perfectly perfect yet
Okay, but psycheverse
org and this is gonna be kind of my answer to the IP to which is a very
Kind of toxic
Network, you know, I mean, I don't nothing's wrong with it. It's just a little bit toxic for my taste and I don't like you know
Calling people low cows and stuff and like you know making fun of people
I mean it's like a little bit making fun of people but like you know
I want to be I just want cool people and like the IP to has turned into like a bunch of like
You know the audience like trying to kill the streamer and I don't like that right? I want it to be like
You know kind of like a friendlier place. Okay, let's let's I mean it will still have some chaos
But like a little bit less chaos. Okay, so here's what it looks like so far
And what do I have on it?
I have, let me see, what do I have on it?
So there's a psyche verse.
Can I make that bigger?
Let me see.
Okay, I can't, okay.
So, here's what it looks like.
Okay, there's the Psykeepers, okay,
and then I can just scroll through it a little bit.
And then see, it shows who's live,
it'll show who's live.
I have, you know, me,
and I'm sorry if I don't have you updated yet,
but yeah, look, I got Summer,
talk your issue up there.
I'm gonna have Traveling Gypsy.
I'm gonna, you know, I'm gonna have everyone listed back.
I'm sorry, I'm just, this is a prototype, okay?
I have more people listed.
But it keeps like, you know, I have to make sure I add it.
We have news there, you can contact,
you can browse the streamers, there's a directory,
you can contact, you can apply to be on it, you know,
and you know, it's gonna be, as long as you're basically,
it's gonna be a cooler thing, okay, it's gonna be cooler.
And I wanna help everybody as much as I can, okay?
And so there you go.
I'm working on this website.
Oh, okay. Oh, no, I wasn't saying you're complaining. I know I know I just felt like you deserved one, right?
Hey, lowrider, I felt like you deserved one because I did like you did you did a really nice
Song for me, too. Like you made a you made a nice song for me. I really appreciate it
I really do appreciate people that are into like this like the creating all
kinds of like, you know cool videos of music and
What however we create it. It's like
I think that mixing the technology plus like the human part of it creates some good stuff. So
that's it. So, um, let me just close this down. Okay.
Anybody coming up? Hey, look, my nails are, well, they're not perfect. I was kind of digging
through tobacco again. I try, I try, I try. They're not terrible. Hey, I got you on there too. I have
I really want to, I hope that, post your channel,
trying to build and hit, yep.
Oh, money, you're modded, you can post your link.
And your channel, no, your channel's on there.
Did you see it?
I can show you again.
Look, you're on there money for, I mean,
there's more people on it.
Like I have like the oceans, woo,
I have DJ Electric's channels and things.
I can show you real quick.
But this is a money for 20s on there. I don't know if this is like right though. Like it says like cryptocurrency and stuff
I don't know but I'll share the screen again. So this is what it says like evers, okay?
See money right there money for 20s at yours. It says financing trip. This is like this came up as your
Name is at your name and stuff. And so if I click that it should go to yeah, that's your channel
right
Bita's channel is not on there because Bita decided that she does not want to be
associated with me or I
Would have loved to I would have loved to but
She decided that you know, she'd rather like talk shit about me than be my friend. And so
and
Then told me today to leave her alone. So
I'll do that
Anyway, you're welcome. Yeah, and everyone subscribe make sure make sure everyone that's a mod you can post your channel
Yeah, there's a yeah burning joint and Nick does a great job of sharing channels. Oh, yeah, Jan will be on there for sure
I see I just I have to add people. That's not yours. Oh shit. Okay. Okay. That's not your channel. It looked kind of like yours
My I was confused hold on
That's your channel
On a mission to hit 500 subs. Look. Oh, that's yours. I mean, I went to the right channel
It's just like I don't know why it's a crypto finance. I have to fix that. Like I said, it's a prototype
I'm like working on it. I can work on it actually tonight
But I need people on the panel real quick so I can go work on it real quick
I can work on it like a little bit a day
because
And only work on a little bit of day, but 50 to go for Santa. Okay, and yeah, of course, I got Janet. I got
Hope maybe Vita and I will make up, but I'm not gonna go to her
Panel anymore. I'm not gonna go over there because it's too
Toxic unfriendly. I get screamed over
I'm willing to work it out, but
I'm willing to
I know I was you know
But I then again guys if you are an expert in the
Carter verse
I'm not trying to get not trying to look up any beat of them all
I'm just like interested in the Carter verse a little bit because I know a friend of Aaron Carter and she was like actually
You know doing some bad stuff with them and stuff maybe got him. I don't know like um, and so I'm kind of curious about some things
Also, I'm curious about the gangstalking aspect of it and I'm curious about
The
I mean the gymnik that was an was that the real gymnik that was on my panel because people were saying that wasn't even the real
Gymnac that was somebody pretending to be her and stuff, right?
That would have been creepy because it sounded just like her it sounded just like her but she was kind of like talking like I
Didn't really expect her to talk like I like I thought she went I didn't think she would say oh
Well, yeah, it's okay that we trolled him to death because
He was on drugs or something that didn't seem like
The gymnik I know
But maybe I'm confused you can tell me about it
Aaron was extremely paranoid and delusional. Okay. Yeah, I know
But was there a reason for him to be because he had a whole community trying to troll him to death basically
I got like that's what the person said like the
They're fake gym neck or real gym next year is like well. Yeah, but he deserved it because he was
He was on drugs. I don't think people just because someone's on drugs
that means that they're easier to like, you know fuck with and
It just kind of just didn't seem like
Nice to me. I just don't like it
If someone was having problems, I mean dr. Phil tried to save his life, you know
Why would people try to like?
kill someone
It doesn't seem like he was gang stocks. I mean like I did play this stuff today. I'll play it again
I'll play it again. I mean, it's like just like
I'll play it one more time. I mean look at my history. It's in my history
I'll play this clip because I found this little clip today of you know, somebody we all know and
Let's see. Where is this?
It's a pretty short clip since no one's coming up. Oh, yeah, here it is. Okay
Person's name is Crystal Ann or something. Here we go. Has anybody heard of Crystal Ann?
I mean she seems like a little bit of a nut, but let's just see what she has to say
Crystal Ann
beat up fuck beat up beta sucks beta you want to fucking play these fucking games
and show up bitch come on for you to sit there and call my friend a fucking rat
no fuck you beta June be the jewels fuck you
You want the pants back or you want to continue blackmailing your ex-friends that you screwed over I don't give a fuck anymore. I'm done
You literally are shitting on Jamie. Who's my fucking friend?
Literally pitting people against each other which is uncool. You're literally fucking crazy
You don't give a shit about me beta when I was in Cali
Not once did you ever let me come to your apartment and we're so-called besties. I
Let you into my life with my mom
Fuck you beta. Hate you
And Rick, if you want to continue talking to Bita, you can lose me, too.
He's a different Jamie.
And you know what I'm going to call it?
There's a fuck Ella and fuck controller.
Fuck them all.
Fuck, I'm sick of the drama.
Maybe stop talking sexually on me, because you were really embarrassing when I was getting my hair done.
It was a really embarrassing call.
And even from an outsider looking in, she even thinks you're the common denominator of pitting people against each other.
So fuck you, Bita. And damn straight, I did tell Gamble we had a fallout.
You want to know why? You threatened to call the police on me. That's why.
Sick of this shit
Just wait
No, you're so good this bitch is nuts
the police on me, but you have my nudes. Weird, right? Okay, go ahead. Do it. Call the calls.
I don't give a fuck. You go from calling the cops to to literally saying happy birthday,
then you sit there and say, Oh, I use you for money.
You're going to throw your gifts into my face from the years before.
Because I got Jamie that ring that ash tray didn't want her to get ash tray
How about I give you your fucking pants back to that I never fucking wore cuz I knew you would do something like this beta. I
Just think she's entertaining
You want to know why you lost all your fucking friends beta because you can't fucking keep a secret that's why
Okay, we'll play the rest later. Hello, Graham. Hello, Mike. How you doing?
I'm just dandy. How are you doing my friends?
recovering from a
Problem with me medication. Oh, I'm sorry. I
Went to a friend's house
About 250 miles away left on me meds at home
without realizing
so I
You know what because the medication is highly addictive
I came off it all of a sudden and jeez, did I pay for it?
Oh my gosh.
But I had to get someone to drive me home, because I couldn't even drive.
Yeah, I've sort of been catching up with this bit of drama that's been going on with an unknown, unnamed person from my point of view.
Drama is part parcel of YouTube. However, you control it. It's your it's your channel
Absolutely, but it goes further than that because it's like we did have a friendship. She was a big part of the show
Yeah, and she's decided to like, you know
Personally go after me up on a lot of stuff that was kind of out of bounds too. And so maybe I get it
I get it and
You don't do drama really
You're best with the tarot cards, that's what one of the reasons why I still come here is because I do like listening to your tarot, to your readings and the one you did for me was more or less spot on at the time, it was great.
And I do plan on like focusing more on...
That I think I got a little bit off track at some point, you know
Mm-hmm involved in the drama and that's like, you know, that's my bad
You know, but I do like love so many people in this community
I'd like you know, it's kind of like I didn't expect it
but it's like, you know, I did fall in love with a lot of people and
Not not just fall in love, but you know, I really do love I know you mean I know
Um, just a quick word on your website, by the way, it's looking good. Thank you. Um, you're gonna be on there
You're right. I I build websites myself. I've got two in the own
One of them I'm rebuilding at the moment because I want to put the radio player on it for the dream radio show
That I want to open up to
Creators who want to have total free speech. Yeah
okay so that they can have a show that can talk as much as they like or play music or whatever
without too many terms and conditions right shall we say and i i agree with that philosophy and it's
like i really like you know i i want basically any if someone wants to be on the website i'll put
them on the website um you know unless i really don't vibe or i don't feel like i vibe with them
Know you don't like the energy. I know you don't like the energy Marcy, but it's like
I've been like kind of piled like if you saw the Shannon stuff earlier like on on on Kate Kate's show
When I was just like this lady was like that fucking bitch psyche kid in a spew and
Put his legs behind his taint and love line
He doesn't know fucking shit about terror and then I tried to do a nice reading for her because I'm you know Barry
Said oh, let's do a reading for you know, I'm doing it for a reading
And then she was just very unkind and saying,
I don't know how to do tarot when I obviously do.
And I'm just sick of being disparaged over it.
And just like a lot of, I know it's a part of this community
is like, but I know I'm different,
and I'm a gay guy in the community.
And so it's like, I'm kind of a little bit different.
She seems, this woman Shannon just seemed very unhinged.
And she got me a little bit, little bit, little bit.
I had
Yeah, I think I was pretty funny though
I think I think I did a good job actually and I thought I was pretty good considering the circumstances
And it was and again five people against me basically everyone egging her on saying that she you know, she's doing
Oh, she's so funny. She's making such great points. And it's like she really wasn't I think I
Basically you heard her the other night. Yeah
And she was talking about KK too and I was actually in KK's channel today this morning
I went in there and I was like hi, and I was like just like, you know hanging out. I love KK
I know KK was but um
People in the chat were like go away psyche. Like what are you doing here? Like what why are you here?
And I was like, I'm not allowed to be here and then like
But this stage was like, oh yeah, you can be here and KK was nice and everything
But just like it was just like so many people just hate me. It seems like and I was like, I don't really know why but
They don't know you so they're going by what they believe from
I do recognize a lot of them from
Yeah, but I mean, you don't actually know them, you know them from the chat and they know you.
The Shannon woman said that she doesn't watch my show, she just saw clips of me.
Yet, she had seen my advertisements, which I, you know, are in my shorts and stuff.
And then she had seen terror readings which aren't really clipped on tripkicking stuff like that
So that's kind of an unusual sound like she does watch the show don't ever apologize for her. Oh, thank you
Thank you
I was I didn't have a kind of a good time and it was kind of like because I do feel like I stuck up for myself
But I mean she was saying pretty nasty things, but I played it like three times
So obviously I think that was kind of funny. It was funny. I know I do like Barry Barry's nice and
generous and friendly and cool. I think he's good in the community. He trolls a little bit, but, you know.
I think it's, you know, anybody who puts a comment in that's not in the supportive way,
they're still putting a comment in the chat, they're still watching and guess what hate is? It all
affects the algorithms and makes it better. So, you know.
There's some comments that have just been like rubbing me the wrong way that I'm just happy to like, you know
Well, especially today, you know, I was like
People were saying oh, we're sending the police to your house. You know the for the past week
I've had people I'm looking for scrap metal banging on my door for all hours of the day
Unpaid pizzas. I can actually show this guy's channel where he shows my front door, you know with my
And everything and it's like and then he's like oh 10 minutes later. Here's another pizza and stuff like that
and um
You know, and I'm pretty, I feel like that's way over the line.
I also had manure, like, you know, 20 bags of manure.
The way I was at my door, I've had every, so many unpaid pizzas.
It's like, what's really the saddest part is that people come,
like this guy came to get scrap metal.
He came with his granddaughter.
You can hear her outside like,
I'm ready to go to the park, grandpa.
And he's like, oh, we're going to get some scrap metal.
And it's like, they're, she's like, okay.
And it's like.
He's just wasting people's time,
wasting these like the restaurant, the food.
I don't know if they get to keep the food.
Hopefully they do.
But it's like, and it's like, people are really nice.
The people that have been sent, they're always like,
oh my God, like, who would do that?
They're like, they're just like,
and it's just like, they look more disappointed than I am
that people are just banging on my door all hours.
That's fucking rude.
And I'm just like, yeah.
And they're stroking the algorithm.
I don't mind if they're trolled me a little bit,
but like some people have been just been like,
I think the experience you had from them, I think that's beyond YouTube, that's harassment,
literally harassment.
And the person, with the day I was like, so people were saying, oh, we're sending the
cops to your house, the SWAT team, blah, blah, blah.
And it's like, so I was like, and I look and the mods weren't hiding them.
And then I would like hide them.
Like timing them out instead like he just like unhiding them time. I say it's like it's my show
It's like if I time them out probably hide them hide the hidden wants have a total right to like hide
Yeah, one stuff I have but Alex also hid like 60 people in my chat, too
And so that was a problem plus Alex just has a
What you call it?
the Saratarian
Um wave doing things he always has done and always will do just the way he is
But he was like so excited. He's like, oh my gosh, I have my own channel and stuff
But he wasn't he was just he said he told me he's like he was just wanting to hide people
That's all he wasn't even talking or on the camera. He just wanted people to come so we could hide them
I mean that's what I think when you're hurt if something's so unhinged and like does that.
Well, if he wants to hide people, he'll never get, it's channeled and never grow. Simple as that, you know.
Yeah, I think he's like, he's like, oh, I give up. Like, he's like, but he just, it was like a trap.
He was trying to set. Plus, he was using my name on it. I was like.
And it was titled psyche awakens TV
That would be so original for him. He did it to wind you up. He was calling up people's podcast
I mean he's like sort of the four like four lives on stream yard within like an hour
all of them just blank, you know, it's just like a blank screen of the stream yard.
Well, I would say the majority of people are welcome when I go live.
I don't care whether they're trolls or not, but if it starts to become personal,
with other people
Then the the mods can do what our own mob people just so that the mods can do what they want
Or this DC, you know, the energy mods time them out and then let me know
And I'll
You know get rid of them get rid of them that way
Pretty bad like I know people have like, you know gotten a pizza once in a while or something but it's been weeks
It's been like weeks of every day
Like stuff happening like at least like when you know one one incident a day sometimes several a day and it's you know
And it's like I know who's doing it
You know the authorities are looking into it
But it's just very hard to per prosecute this kind of stuff and it's like people are in different states and you know
It's like this is a big hassle. I would just prefer
Of course, you know, people grow up and like, you know, it's the person's obsessed with me
If you see his channel, it's just like all my show and all
The thing is
some people use
Imitation as a way of flattery orders use it as a way of
Showing their true colors, right? Okay. I want to show you just like two minute clip of like actually
And Chanel gets it right bad jealous people
uh, can be petty
Agree. Yep. Yep. And this person like I think this person was once like, you know, kind of
LOL cow or whatever people took, you know, try kind of making an LOL cow embarrassed him
And now he has a chance to like try to make me one. Unfortunately. I just can't be what I'm not, you know
It's like so, I mean, it's like if I was, you know, I mean, it's like maybe I'm done some like stupid shit
But it's like I'm kind of like
you know aware of that but here is um oh yeah and okay so I'm just gonna show this really quick
clip this is like it's only a minute one minute 38 seconds and this channel is full of this
and here you can just get an example of what I had to deal with I think I was on the air yeah I was
on the air so let me see I'm just gonna share this real quick oh real quick hey Nick what's up
Did I just kick Nick off? Oh, no, I didn't. Okay, so share screen and here's what it looks like.
This is an average day on my show. Saiki gets visitors, it's called. Here we go.
Okay, he's frosting, right? It tastes like... Hello? Who is it? Who is it?
Is it paid for? Yolanda? Is it paid for? No. Okay, no, I didn't order it. I'm sorry.
pizza for Jolanda yeah but I didn't order anything I think might be a prank
okay yeah it might be a prank
hopefully you get to keep it have a good day
Can you just can someone please fucking pay for the pizza, please? Oh, I'm sorry
I would have I supposed to let you back up. Can someone pay for the pizza, please like don't stop sending me not paid for pieces
It's so rude. You pay for the fucking manure. Why can't you pay for the pizza?
My friend door
Was it what's that kiddie's name?
And even baby girl
Baby you're paid for baby. Oh, baby girl. Okay. This is just a collective for you, right?
Is it paid for is it paid for?
No, that's it it's a prank it's a prank. I'm sorry. I didn't order anything
Yeah, yeah, there we go that's that
Oh, at the end of the day, all the dude is pissing off the pizza delivery driver.
Very rude.
Oh, we have Aiden here.
I'm going to put the banner up real quick because Aiden is here.
I'm not sure if I know this person one sec yet.
Okay.
Aiden.
Hello?
Is there an Aiden in the house?
You have five seconds to say something or you're getting kicked out Aiden five
four
Three up. Hold on. Hello Aiden
Say something. I
Saw you come on camera say something
Okay, obviously some douchebag, okay ban from studio. Thank you very much. Okay. That takes care of that. Okay
Hey Nick, how you doing?
Hey Nick. Oh, he's building
He's building a bong a bong building you can control yourself and your actions you can't control
I know I can't I know I can't but it's like this person is also
You know fucking with friends of mine putting their
I'm not even gonna get into it, but yeah, there's just a lot of doxing going on. That was a porn bomb loser
Yeah, name Aiden and you know what?
I haven't been porn bombed in like months because I'm too fast for it now
Okay, and it's like so don't even bother. Okay. I know people and so I know who to like I mean I'm gonna like
I just I just I'm just I'm just getting too good at it. I haven't been porn bomb successfully in a long time
Yeah, well, I think is you know, you look at what you can't control not what you found and the only worry about what you can't control
Right, I mean
You you can't you control that that's fine. You can't control others
Right, I'm not trying to control my own panel though. You know, it's like a yes exactly and you can control your chance
and I can like a banner and
No, make sure that I know them and have them say something and look at them in the case
And if I don't know them and they have no reason to be there and look someone tried to come up
Okay, no, no, I heard so I mean, it's like it's just like the people are just wasting their time
It's just so sad wasting everyone's time. That's all it's about. It's like
I'm willing to have a conversation. I'm willing to fucking do free readings. I mean come up
It's like what say something more interesting than trying to put, you know, big black dildo up on the screen or whatever
Yeah, yeah, I'm getting that one
I mean, unless it's like, you know, really good, it's usually never getting good porn.
It's like, it's like always like some disgusting porn is like, put some like, get some like,
you know, Jenna Jamison or something like, I don't know, something better than whatever
that was.
It was just like, oh, no, ooh, yeah, what they forget is that you can actually record
If they ever come back, you can always show it to them.
Look, you idiot, did it this and just blur out what the show is like, it doesn't affect
your channel.
It does bother me that it's like there might be someone watching that really doesn't want
to see that or like we're really like, you know, like.
I don't I don't want anybody like to see it's like almost like a
Violation to have like a porn show when you're not wanting to see porn, right? It's like it's not supposed to be so I don't know
It's kind of like hurting everybody
Except I don't know. I feel like it's pretty crazy. That's a pretty insane bong. Nick. I want to see a bong hit. That's like a pretty
I was a sex boy for a second. That would be fun
I can just imagine sitting on that I'm just kidding. I'm not such a
What he's gonna, but he's going to bone good to channel
I mean I can always you know in the street
No
Yes, you guys see auto the other day that was pretty fun
You see flirty diamond and auto that was one of the classic episodes of my show when flirty diamond and auto came and auto admitted that
He wants to bend over for Fruity Diamond, like he really was like that into, I mean, he's a straight guy, but actually then he started squirting lotion on his like, you know, bare chest and it kind of made me so sick that I think I'm just done with sex all together.
You know, I thought it was gay, but
and then I'm not going to be your asexual asexual now I'm just done with this I just
like discuss it without the human body at this point I'm just kidding um I'm not joking
I think I think now she wants to see the bong on full screen yeah okay I got you I got you here
let's let's watch nick for a minute here I'm gonna let you guys oh here we go here we go okay
Nick is always showing some interesting stuff.
Okay, I like that.
I didn't like that.
I don't know how it's gonna work, but I can't wait to see.
Careful.
Yeah, but I actually did have a good day. It's a brilliant piece of work. I hope it works. I
Do too I would love to like is that like a double-headed bong though. I've heard of a double-headed
I want to know how he's going to like it and smoke it
Nick do it. Oh, please demonstrate. I would love to see it
That's a big water container. I mean he has I mean I think I've seen it like 50 bar
I mean I want to make are you gonna send me a custom bomb, please?
Yeah, I'll say I'll pay for shipping. I
Will and I'll pay for materials and stuff. I'll pay for your you know the craftsmanship to
Hello, and I I can't I can't pause a little bit expensive these days, but
Do my best. Oh
By the way, yeah, I do have like my Etsy store open. I'm a psyche awakens on Etsy
I have several readings there or you can just contact me privately and something like that
You can work out something if you want to but yeah
I know people interested in like I'm mixing the astrological and tarot with you know actual
some AI generated art and music that is custom to
people's like Sabian symbols, astrological sign, and it's like, you know, completely like making
really cool stuff. I've done it for Spunky and a few other people, and it just comes out really,
really cool. I think it's like very unique. And so if you'd be interested in that, you'd have your own
song, you'd have your own, you know, collection of art, and it's a way of really immersing yourself
in, you know, your astrological profile and things like that. And so I
Just hit me up for that.
Also, if you'd like, you know, a reading tonight,
if you don't want a reading, I'm happy to do a reading.
Wow, oh shit, my...
Okay, yeah, I have to do some stuff on my own for this, for this website, okay, so I'm going to do that later, okay.
So is that, but you like the song I made? You saw the song earlier, the Lilith song? I don't know if you like that.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Also, so you use music and well, AI music, she'll be saying, right?
Are you writing the lyrics and then I put it through?
the music thing. Yeah, you're using AI as a tool. Right. It's like it's perfect when you mix, you
know, you know, which there's nothing wrong with. I mean, I use AI for my music. The wife on her
channel, she uses AI music. The record industry uses, the record industry uses plenty of, you know,
synthesizers and vocal AI. I mean, I think there's so much, I mean, kind of Donna
It always amuses me when people turn around and say, well, that's AI, blah, blah, blah,
but yeah, the music industry uses and has used.
It doesn't generate itself.
Electronics.
I see the right thing.
But.
OK, there's a difference between AI music and record music.
There's also a difference between record music and live music.
You go to a live show, and that is where you see musicians and singers.
Yes, in the background there will be different amplifiers and tuners and whatnot, but it still raw sound.
Like yes
Yeah, but what I'm saying is I guess there's nothing wrong with using a eye. It's like everything else. It's a tool
Yeah, hi, Goddy
Instruments and so I'm afraid I got some bad news
I'm gonna get in my my room room and you're not going to like it
Tell me rim. Here's my rim
This is my rim reaper. You're all going to die
Well
That's kind of obvious though. We all are right. I love just thinking I'm gonna say why do you think I'm here?
Tell me you say it's about yourselves. I'm just booking you in for later
Soul is reserved for
So she gets first tips, then whatever she doesn't eat, you get.
I'm just kidding.
Yep, just me and Nick at the moment, it's like he's just dropped off.
And Nicky is building the equivalent of the Empire State Building in a bong.
He's worked out his mistake and now he's working on how to get it, right
Nick
Nick it might be easier to connect the bomb the bottom part of the bomb first
I'm like no me talking about me not you. Oh
Why don't you want to say things so?
Contradictory
me
I just think it's a great pieces of architecture
The loose hairs outside of the ear and everything who you think you are
Albert Einstein, I am hoping that works
I'm going to show that to you, Albert.
Okay.
Do I have to turn that fan off?
Somehow, it's too hard to get over there.
She's in the way.
I'm surrounded by balls.
I've also seen a master builder. I do like seeing a master builder. I also like watching things when they go wrong.
Oh, thank God. Half of that dog.
That's my eyeballs. My bum didn't have eyes anymore. So I was all excited about that.
And I didn't take much.
I don't know. Where are we go?
near direction.
Oh, this cat hair is in the
bowl. The cats love for you to
smoke their hairs. It's
ridiculous. Don't walk around on
As long as it needs to be super glued on the ends, whichever one you want to settle in
In it
Got a piece regardless water. Oh
But you need some scaffolding around it to keep it in one place
There we go, here we go, here we go
If this works, I hope you'll be able to give you a big round of applause.
At least get the free promo on the pipe.
Oh, shit. Then we put this on the tray. I don't know if you can see it says no shirt in the
should've probably put some white paper behind that, but I know.
Fuck.
Easy, good to see you.
Who's in charge around here?
Yeah, not me.
I was gonna get my assistant, Susan, on that.
Susan, you're fired.
Clean out your fucking locker.
I have kids.
I don't get much shit.
Tell them there's no Christmas this year because mommy didn't do her job, right?
Hey, I don't do Christmas. I do Halloween
That's my time. Yeah, the beginning of October fast the first of the month of October
Yeah, I always want to participate, but I always find out about it too late. They're like talking about it in the newspaper
And I'm like, yeah
Yeah, no we drank, but it was just like
High school parties, you know like for that. What was it?
Junior year or some shit
Just be like fucking go to different
school's parties and just like crashing up like taking over that shit with our
school you're like fuck yeah our football team is kicking your football
team's ass and some of your fucking dudes would come in like fight their school
and then we have to like leave before the cops came you know I don't mean you're
just drunk just drunk you don't even know people driving you around your
friends driving you around you're trying not to throw up in a passenger seat
You know talk about the window talk about the window
Yeah, I don't drink fuck that shit. Where's the remote? This is a skeleton of what it used to be
What the hell
Even our remotes are leaving us, you know, like what we used to have
took all the shit they just took all the personal shit from it, you know
What the hell is doing I
Can't do I can't turn the TV up. I can't turn it down. I
Can't turn it all around. I can't put one foot in I can't put one foot out. I can't turn myself about
Oh, I thought you did yelkey-cokey
Man, we do this all the time
Darrel says rents of a matman
Man, what the hell's that remote? I thought it's not under my act. I don't feel it. It's a little remote, but it ain't dead down
No, I don't
As you would they're getting so small I can't even find them if you're sitting on
I used to under a bridge
Yeah. Many years ago, when I
when I lost, yeah, when I lost
the remote many years ago, I
I had remotes to look for the
remote to call children. Oh
yeah, we used to have a
clapper for the key. Yeah,
there she go. I think we lost
that shit or it stopped beeping.
We need to get that shit on
everything. Just
Yeah
Maybe he's gone off to do a few things on the computer
The same one is homegirls was on a lot of
check-and-see
You gotta go to Emma Levite and
Check-and-see if you shout out. You don't care if I shout out these people though
Well, if he shouted out there's no way I can stop me even if I did even if I wanted
I can't exactly do anything. Let's face it. No, I got high on that last it
But I think
Trey a bunch of bullshit and so I call it Normandy because you'd be like if you was in Normandy
You'd smoke anything
You know, so you'd be like, oh, come on. You know, like you like in the in the war and they're like shooting at you or somebody
Oh shit, it's makes like here. Here. This shit you go. Oh fuck. Yeah
That's like in my head. I just kind of like tell myself it's some Normandy, but you know, it's all on the tray and shit
Mm-hmm bunch of shit
I'm just like smoke that shit like during the war
And just like yeah
You gotta just like put yourself in the trenches.
And now look, that's what happened.
You got me fucked up.
Now it's like some magical shit.
So you know when you thought 20, sorry, it's, you know, like,
I'm just me and Nick.
So, he's looking for his remote
So, we can sort out his TV.
Move around. Let's move around.
So, we find it. Oh, so it's
I can still hear. So, let's go
out. We're missing remote.
Listen, if that can help me, I
will say to you in the last
place you look. Right. It's
I'm on the track
Whenever I'm rolling something you have to lose the paper and then you like look underneath like a magazine or whatever you're rolling on
Mm-hmm. That's where the paper is and you'll be like
That's what happens more times than I can throw a rocket. Oh
Shit the other balls there, I'm sorry, baby. Oh
They didn't need to have money money for 20 you're right. It's always in the last place. You look
That's how it's down stupid. It's just if you if you if you went there first that you wouldn't be looking
Got it, it's count. It's this countdown to the best time of the year
In my opinion and that is Halloween itself
Yeah, yeah, Christmas Thanksgiving and Halloween
Not necessarily in that order
Well, I don't do we well we don't do Thanksgiving over here
to be thankful for
but
Halloween is the most sacred time of year for me when all of the
Ghouls come out
and you can spot the ghoul track ghouls so easily you know
ghouls what comes out ghouls ghouls yeah not just souls ghouls
I bet it's crazy over in England for halloween
well yes and no but you see I'm not going to be here over halloween
Um, I'm still staying in within in Great Britain, but I'm going over to Northern Ireland and I'm hoping to be able to do a live on
old
Halloween Eve
and
Do what I usually do and piss about on on the show. I was like, I'm gonna do a line
If I do a live not a line
Yeah. Me and the wife got married on the 31st of October. I think I sang some line. But yeah, Halloween is a very sacred time of year for the Reaper. So yeah, it's always good.
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
We wait, we wait in anticipation.
Are you a piece of shit?
Ladies and gentlemen, don't try this at home.
Unless you know what you're doing.
Welcome Steph and Sean.
ladies and gentlemen it was worth the wait it worked then that worked well
didn't it? It's hard! I put some tape around around the edges or the
connections just so that it doesn't escape you know you get the full
because you don't want to try to hold it. I found a roll of duct tape.
It was outside. I said, what?
But then the duct tape looks too official.
I got a clear tape. Yeah, clear tape works.
Yeah. Yeah, I could smell. I could smell a lot over here.
I love talking people from
Johnny's right. Yeah. Hey, I'm over here. You know what? It's like I
Love this shit. It just sounds more proper
This is like English
And we know I don't speak I don't think the Americans speak English
No, they speak American
Yeah, it's American English
That's why I want to get back to like some real English ass shit, you know, like some Shakespeare
You know, oh god. No, you don't what you don't want that crap
Well, you know what I'm saying
The English people where I'm like, oh, you know Hugh Lorre and shit can get on stage and start
Motherfucker he'll get on stage and start spit. Well, he ain't never say shit is being
Well, it's a funny thing, right? Okay. You want to do you want to speak English or do you want to learn English as a difference?
Because American English and English are two different languages
Believe it or not. Well, it's changing every day. Yeah. Well, there's something I
Say that because the way you spell things
phonetically in other words how they sound not how they're actually spelt because
There are silent use that we that are in the English language, you just take them out, which is good. It all makes sense, but I do find it funny.
Only because I know if I if I asked Nicky to spell the word color, he probably would spell it C-O-L-O-R, not C-O-L-O-U-R.
Yeah, but you know what? It's all in the day's work
Man you got to come on more
What's your name again?
What's your name again? Let's call me grim. Oh
It's trim re I think I put you in the rat that I made for sight
Yeah, quite possibly
Yeah, I was dropping all these names in there and psych wasn't feeling it because it wasn't made by AI at all
It's like
Fuckers and making other songs
If you wrote
Yeah, but if you write write the music the lyrics you can always put it into an AI to get the music to go with it
on how they did that shit. Yeah. I think I could send it to
Sight and he could make it but it was really though. This was
pushing the envelope because I was like dropping H bombs.
It was pushing the envelope but it was all out of love.
Yeah, it's like I don't think psych was feeling it though. We still got I would like to make a music video
But it just seems like a lot of work
The music videos are like to make a really good one like some of the videos I have is kind of expensive to be joining
It's like, you know, I think to make some of the
15 bucks or whatever to generate like a really high quality video, but I can make other kinds of videos like with like, you know
Not as
Complex and cool, but still pretty cool. Like the haters club one
Dude, oh, you're welcome Johnny. My pleasure
You saw that. Yeah, I can't even breathe because I breathe too loud
Hey everybody in chat, I have that problem I just stopped breathing
I've got brain damage. Oh good. Yeah, absolutely
If I had the brain as some people would put it, it would be damaged
Lack of oxygen for so many years
Yeah
There's a lot of people who live in their own bubble and that's all they ever breathe is their own air
And you get to a point where they believe that they are actually good people
Anyway, move it gone
Enough air time for that
Good to see you back in and joining the psyche. So it says the government has shut down for the first time in five years
What's going on? What did they shut down?
It says government shuts down for first time in five years. Let me see it says
Yeah, there's a fox news story. So the government fox news senior correspondent report
Down is the gun it's a
Government shut down guys. Oh, that's not good use
Oh, that means that hey, that's to stop all the auditors from going in on
public property
Let's just sit down
No, I think Charlie Kirk was gonna be president before all this after after that happened
I start looking at things and I go do I think he was gonna be president at some point later on down the roof
just at least like a
Like no, I could see it. Like it sounds crazy now, but it's like what does it work?
Unfortunately, we'll never know
You know, but he had he's got you know, he had he just went he just said stuff from his heart and from his
Incredible
Rain that could recall facts and figures didn't need to get Google it or anything like that. He just knew it
And you know
Personally, I didn't agree with everything he said, but I would never wish that on anyone
Yeah, I think he's like the new Martin Luther King Jr. I'm sure man the way it's like if you look at it
It was like very similar. I honestly believed that possibly
There is some sort of cover-up
Not saying anything about JFK, but you never know. No, no Martin Luther King, Jr.
Yes, JFK similar all that shit. Mm-hmm
Anybody who starts to speak out and goes against the narrative
One way or another ends up
and the carry of situations, you know, they always say everybody that says anybody that says they want to bring everybody together
Yeah
Well, I like the idea of bringing John living together
Mark David Chapman
You know so on and so on. I'm so fucking high. They don't like what am I doing? But we don't know
James out
We have to
Like psyche is working on his website while we have the bodies up there
I want Joker to come back on
Upload that shit
here. I missed those little uh
what are those little
I was like you come on over and
like promote your show and stuff.
I love to see those dogs and
those little Prince Charles. I
see people's dogs out. I'm like
oh Prince Charles because
I'd be like knowing all the dog
breeds. I don't know. It's weird.
Like how do I know all the dog?
Well, I've got a cabbage wet mister Abbey fucking judge or some shit
I've got a cabbage on
Dog and she's absolutely brilliant. So though at times very noisy
Which she was earlier. She saw somebody walking past the window
So she goes in defensive mode just the way she is
Yeah
I mean I ain't got no more but
Now cats are the new dog. I
Love all animals. I think animals
especially cats are very very truthful and very honest
They pick you as they're as part of their pack
whereas a dog
recognizes you automatically as
You are he is or she is your pet
I don't know if I've heard about it.
Yeah, is that is that message?
Grab what they used to do.
What?
What were you saying? Just go on.
Darrell, man is best friend, foot gats. Well, personally, I wouldn't
but whatever, you know, I mean, let's keep it clean folks.
Yeah, my problem is animals like me
Doesn't matter where I go they automatically come to me and
It is quite amusing especially when the person I've gone to see turns around says but they never go to anybody
Yeah, like what's that what's that I can't even remember that cartoon snow white or some shit
It's it's it's it's it's it's
it's it's it's it's it's it's
Oh folks, it's not true. I am not related in any way to Dr. Doolittle. I did not talk to animals
Well, I do
What do you understand me? That's another thing
Oh shit, this is a bitch
Johnny is just attempting to get a better bum kit
allegedly
Oh, I love it. My life's uh a conspiracy. Hey, you don't have to be paranoid, but if you are it bloody well helps
It's so hard to pick in the buzz
Wait till grandma wakes up, smoke some Normandy and tell them
We'll go to weed war
Our lighters are going out. We only got this one. It's a one star general
There's a little gold star on here. It's kind of fucking off. Hiya, Queen
Welcome to the chat
There's not a lot going on here we just got Nikki trying to work build the biggest bong in the world
The most stable bong is in the world isn't gonna happen today though
and it's like he's got that
Oh. Oh, that's nice. Okay, thank God.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you. Jamie's asking does Erby get his wrench back? I think it's when you did that clear out
I saw Erby, I don't know, you know, Bondsburg, I mean, it's like you're well to be there, I just don't know if you were like kind of teasing me, I don't know
Um, were you nice? I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I hate being petty, but
Yeah, I don't I don't like Jimmy keeps an eye out for like
Where's he? I thought she was coming by today make the beds. I'm under stress right now
There's a Nick is he's no sink. It's the captain factor. Sorry crypto factor
Oh, I was just ordering one of my pizzas that I got from site local. Oh
Was it paid for I
Never got well, the only person ever sent me paid for food was you know, both actually
Oh
I'll say Alexander McQueen did send me a crab boil one night and it was paid for so thank you
That's actually pretty good. It was a wonderful and other people have sent me
Over here. Yeah, I was actually I don't know if they want me to tell who it was, but someone sent me a nice
Apple juice
I'm a very lucky person.
What are those cucumbers do to
you? I think they get you extra
stupid. Um I thought we'd locked
up the rim Reaper. He's a he's a
bit of a an absolute. I mean,
Oh, come on. Come on. Just let
him on. Grim in rim. Come on.
Oh, I got the bread. Is that
real? Yes, that is a real
over here on 16
Y'all want to see the box that I got this body. Where's that fucking box?
What did we do with it now?
I remember the captain factor
Well, Erby's got a big following in the chat. A lot of people like him.
Well, he's got a wrench.
And not only do I remember the crafting factor, I remember rolling three paper joints.
Type it again. Type it again, Erby.
And that was before they had the big risler papers.
What are you trying to do there?
It's the original blonde. Yeah, you need into this shape
After I got it for free on the curve
So we did have a yard game that we made out of it and it was cool as hell
Well, my favorite yard games. I say this yard game right here. Don't ever stop. Oh
shit
Look, I'm gonna call the company
My son of a bitches. He did me wrong for the last time
Warning choking hazard small parts do not smoke if you're a stupid skateboard. What the fuck
They put that shit on the box
Are you kidding me
I'm fucking pissed now
I'm pissing
pissing pissed that they have the audacity
to come at me
side ways on the box
if I wasn't eating the redone
the best pizza
right now
I wouldn't be so pissed
Don't think we down to be we got the best pizza
your kids after soccer
Oh God, we'll be almost there. I'm almost there. I'm almost there. I think I'm almost got it. They don't got the best pizza
Man, what's up yo?
What?
We got a beach
Damn y'all crazy over there
I think she had a spinal problem after that though.
I don't know if I could walk like too much.
She would beat me.
Let's just say, I can't beat you.
Let's just not play that game.
Hell no.
What the hell were they doing with people's back? Let's see how many people got Google how many people got injured off the yard game
Just doing it walking past it in the store
Ain't just three and up
They think three year olds can play this
Crazy as hell. Yeah, you're old enough to have spinal damage. Come on, Billy
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, no, it wasn't good eating, it's not on the table, all right, just like this please.
Oh, so let's get the TV channels shaped up.
Oh, stupid bottle.
Ah, I just...
That's it. That's it. That's it.
We're going to switch off strong.
Yeah, over here. He's going to work it out.
Okay. Hey, come on, you guys.
I'll try again.
Oh, shit.
What's your list up?
If there wasn't so many, freaking parks, freaking Eli Whitney,
inventor of the Tottengin, he was like, oh, let's make interchangeable parks. Thanks a lot.
When I was in college
I didn't go to college. All right, duh, we could tell we could tell you don't need to tell
No, I mean I went to our college they like get off campus before we yeah
I was like, oh shit, not somebody else
Whatever you do
Please oh for the love of God. No, don't tell somebody
I'm actually campus security and I'm undercover for both of you are fucking I can't even say you're fucking fired
It's gonna be so funny
Do that the paperwork?
What are your names? How about that?
Of course maybe campus security
Oh, yeah, they got pretty good
It's looking wrong though, it's stinkler than I remember
Oh, I think you're gonna end up making a
Swap stick on the way it's going
Shes look like it's halfway there. Oh
Shit, you're right. This looks bad
Let's take it apart
Glad somebody mentioned that in the chats
We got some of it. All right, these are just carp
We got multiple carp
Now like a finger one of those Chinese finger lock
I need somebody else to put their thumb in there and then
There's a clamp to Jen clamp it
All right, there's some glue or tape
Where's it? Oh
Much work
You get me caught the tape
I'm going to climb up and ash.
Let's just tape it.
No biggie.
Ash.
Somebody pushed me.
Is there a fucking ghost over there?
I was sat here listening to, uh,
psyche, it's not psyche, so, uh,
Nikki going on regarding what's going on.
I think the tape folded over on the bottom.
We'll work with it
All right, I appreciate it. All right, that's too fucking long for me to get my neck back. I'll hold this at the same time
Welcome to the jungle and okay
I don't know. I don't know.
don't know. I don't know. I
Oh, it's like a 50 inch ball.
We're smoking all the ash today.
Normandy style. Let's get stupid
and go on. Okay, stupid. Oh,
shit. I'll be back in a minute,
folks. I'm so sorry. I'm just
So
Okay, I'm gonna play the video and then I'm gonna get right the video
It's made this TV like this. Oh, yeah, well, I don't want to like
Play the song I'll keep you on this one week in line
user
I
Was born with shadows climb the throne
Ten thousand eyes, but I stood alone
Every scar a secret
Carrying stones that cut to the bone they said ambition
She
That's shit. I mean the song was good. It's always good, bro
The bone it's lit on it though
It was quite the experiment but the experiment
you the one I've been missing in my sleep
She's gutting trout, he's eating steak
Somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol
Old page, don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Blend our fl